[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is one of the film companies that produced the film Over Her Dead Body?", "correct_answer": "Gold Circle Films", "incorrect_answers": ["Bowlfry Films", "Little Fish Films", "Silver Lightbulb Films"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What continent has the highest human population density on Earth as estimated in 2007?", "correct_answer": "Asia", "incorrect_answers": ["Europe", "North America", "South America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the treatment of what serious disease is the isotope gold-198 used?", "correct_answer": "Cancer", "incorrect_answers": ["Rabies", "Alzheimers disease", "AIDS"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many songs did Corey write about her ex-boyfriend Joe in the movie Say Anything?", "correct_answer": "65", "incorrect_answers": ["60", "55", "50"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1991 movie won the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture?", "correct_answer": "Hudson Hawk", "incorrect_answers": ["Nothing But Trouble", "Cool as Ice", "Return to the Blue Lagoon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the spoiled rock star Shane Gray in the Disney movie Camp Rock?", "correct_answer": "Joe Jonas", "incorrect_answers": ["Jordan Francis", "Daniel Fathers", "Demi Lovato"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Only about 40% of the moons surface is visible from Earth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In these fractions, used by ancient Egyptians, the numerator is 1 and the denominator is a positive integer.", "correct_answer": "unit fractions", "incorrect_answers": ["algebraic fractions", "decimals", "continued fractions"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Cal marry Carley in the movie Talladega Nights?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the only marsupial in the world that has a backwards pouch?", "correct_answer": "wombat", "incorrect_answers": ["kangaroo", "echidna", "koala"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the last word that Charles Foster Kane utters before his death in the 1941 movie Citizen Kane?", "correct_answer": "Rosebud", "incorrect_answers": ["Buttercup", "Blossom", "Hyacinth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Once a tropical cyclone reaches wind speeds of at least 39 mph, it is classified as a tropical storm. At what minimum wind speed is a tropical storm classified as a hurricane or typhoon?", "correct_answer": "74 mph", "incorrect_answers": ["52 mph", "85 mph", "92 mph"]}]